In the lead,
the left-side competition
(Penny:)Wow, you're really
good at this.
(Amy:)Well, I have an extremely
low center of gravity.
(Amy:)I'm like a pyramid.
(Penny:)How you doing over there?
(Leonard:)Oh, I hope it's just a sprain.
(Leonard:)I cannot walk into that ER
(Leonard:)with another video game injury.
(Penny:)Hey, Sheldon,
you want to play next?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I would,
but I'm on my way out.
(Leonard:)-Where?
-Texas.
(Amy:)Right now? Why?
(Leonard:)-Is someone sick?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)My sister's uterus came
down with a baby.
(Penny:)Oh, she's pregnant?
That's great.
(Penny:)You're gone an uncle--
Uncle Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)No, I will be Uncle Dr. Cooper.
(Amy:)How come you never said
she was pregnant?
(Sheldon:)Well, I never told you
about my brother's kidney stone.
(Sheldon:)You want to hear about everything
(Sheldon:)that comes out
of my family's genitals?
(Leonard:)Well, congrats, and it's nice
(Leonard:)you're gonna be
there for your sister.
(Sheldon:)Yes. I'm filling in for her
husband who's recovering
(Sheldon:)from a horrible motorcycle accident.
(Sheldon:)Lucky duck.
(Penny:)Wow, so, how long will you be gone?
(Sheldon:)Well, she's due tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)Although it did take her
six years to finish high school,
(Sheldon:)so who knows?
(Amy:)Can I give you a ride to the airport?
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, thank you, I don't want
to be an inconvenience.
(Sheldon:)Chop-chop, Leonard.
We leave in ten minutes.